[theme music playing]
[zombies snarling]
- [yelps]
- [Gye-young] Oh, shit.
[shouts, screams]
- [zombie hisses]
- [Soo-jeong continues yelping]
[zombie snarls]
- Oh, God. Okay, let's go.
- [Soo-jeong screams]
Go. It's okay. Keep moving. Go!
Just hurry. Shit.
- [Soo-jeong panting]
- Hey, Soo-jeong.
- [distant thudding]
- Keep crawling.
- Shit!
- [thudding]
- What's that?
- [Soo-jeong] Come on.
[Gye-young] Soo-jeong.
Come on! Hurry! Hurry, Hurry, Hurry!
- Go!
- [screams] Oh, my God.
[distant growling]
- What's going on?
- [both] Zombies.
- Zombies, zombies.
- [Gye-young] They're getting close. Move!
- Shit.
- Ge back, we gotta hurry.
- [Gye-young] Get out of the way.
- [grunting]
Oh, hey. What's going on you guys?
- Zombies.
- [Young-man] Wha... What?
- [Kyung-sik] Zombies.
- [Soo-jeong screams]
[Gye-young] Keep moving. [screams]
[Young-man] Where are you going?
We're going this way.
Over here. Come on.
- [Kyung-sik grunting]
- [Young-man] Hey!
Shit. Be careful coming down.
Shit. Go!
[both panting]
What? Why aren't you going?
[Young-man] Huh?
It's blocked off.
[zombies snarling]
Shit.
[Young-man] Hey! Hold on.
Where are you going?
[both grunting, panting]
What the hell?
[frightening music playing]
Get down!
- [both yelp]
- [yells]
[zombies growling]
[gunshots firing in distance]
- What was that?
- Wait.
- [all breathing shakily]
- Something happened.
Sergeant Kim Young-man.
Come in, Sergeant Kim Young-man
- [radio static whooshing]
- Corporal Kwak Gye-young?
- [radio beeping]
- Shit. Those were gunshots.
Yeah. What else could it be?
- I'm gonna go check.
- Hey, hey!
- What?
- Even if he did it, it'd be too--
- We gotta--
- Stop!
Hey! Believe me.
At this point there's no more going back.
There's no way in hell we'd make it.
We just gotta believe
that they made it out alive.
- [Paolo grunts]
- Huh?
What the fuck? What're we doing? Go, go!
- Fucking go!
- [Arron Park] Hey!
At least we can still try
not to die up here!
Come on! Move it
or lose it, you dickheads.
Paolo!
Hey, Paolo.
[Arron Park panting]
- [Paolo screams]
- [all exclaiming]
- [zombies growling]
- [screams]
What the hell? [yelps]
- [zombies growling]
- [Young-joo screaming]
Oh my god, go away!
[screams, yelps]
[growling]
[screaming, crying]
Holy fuck! [screams]
[screaming continues]
[zombie snarls]
THAT'S CHEATING!
I'm not sorry!
Why would I care about that?
- [screams]
- [zombie 1] Young-joo.
Stay back!
Let's not use the equipment!
[zombie 1] That's not fair.
Don't try to make sense of it!
It's not cute.
- [zombies growling]
- [yelling]
[Young-joo screams]
[grunting]
- [yells]
- [zombies growling in distance]
[Young-joo whimpers]
[yelling]
[snarling]
[continues yelling]
Shit! [crying]
Get away from me, you zombie assholes!
- [yelping]
- [thrilling music playing]
- [zombies snarling]
- [Young-joo screaming]
[panting]
- [zombies snarls]
- [Young-joo grunts]
[chainsaw whirring]
Oh, my God! [yelping]
[grunting]
- [zombies snarling]
- [yelping]
- [growls]
- [grunts]
- [thudding on door]
- [panting]
[grunting]
[exhales]
[breathing heavily]
[exhales sharply] Oh, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
[sighs] Let's take a break here.
Just a couple of minutes.
A couple of minutes.
[exhales]
- [Young-man] Hey!
- Shit.
- [thudding]
- [Young-man pants]
[Kyung-sik blows air]
[Young-man exhales]
[Gye-young breathing shakily]
[Paolo screaming] Help, help.
Fucking help me.
Hurry! Hurry! [yelps]
We gotta help.
- [Paolo yelping]
- [Jae-yoon] Paolo.
Please help! [screams]
[all] Whoa!
[screaming]
[both exclaiming]
[Paolo] Bit my fucking ear.
- [gunshot fires]
- [Paolo] My fuckin' ear. [cries]
Shit, my ear. My ear.
[DEEP IN THE MOUNTAINS]
WHEN THINGS AREN'T GOING WELL,
AND THE MATTERS ARE GETTING WORSE.
[Paolo crying in pain]
Paolo.
- [In-ho] Are you okay?
- What do I do?
- Help me.
- You'll be okay.
No, wait, wait. Wait, wait, wait. Hold on.
He'll turn any minute,
the bite's near his brain!
Not yet. I just had a thought.
He isn't turning.
Arron Park's not a zombie.
What if Paolo doesn't turn?
I think we should wait.
- [squeaks] There's no time to wait.
- Not yet.
Don't do this.
- Please help me.
- I think I know what to do.
[Paolo] Oh, my God! [sobs]
[indistinct clattering]
[Arron Park] Hold him up.
Paolo, here. Take this
and you'll be just fine, okay?
No, but the bite was near his brain.
We're too late.
Goddamn. How could you give up so easily?
[Paolo growling]
[Arron Park] Paolo? Paolo?
- Is he okay?
- [Arron Park] Hey!
[Jae-yon] Huh?
[all exclaiming]
- [growling]
- [all screaming]
[Jae-yoon and In-ho yell]
- [Arron Park] I'm sorry.
- [In-ho and Jae-yoon] Sorry!
[all] Paolo!
[grunting]
[panting]
Shit.
[zombies snarling]
[gun clicks]
[gasps]
- [whispers] Hold on.
- What's going on?
- Shh.
- [snarling continues]
- Zombies.
- Holy shit! This is bad.
Fuck.
[sighs] Oh, my goodness.
[clatters]
[hissing]
Shit.
- Oh, my God.
- Kyung-sik. Oh, God.
[snarling]
[Kyung-sik grunts]
- Kyung-sik, get back!
- [Kyung-sik panting]
[snarls]
Son of a bitch. This mag isn't going in.
[grunts]
- [high-pitched ringing]
- [zombies growling]
[ringing continues]
- [Soo-jeong breathing shakily]
- [Kyung-sik sighs]
Holy shit, man.
[exhales sharply]
[grunts]
[radio feedback cooing]
This way, please. Wonderful guests.
We're over here.
This is Eden Hotel's
Chief Manager, Arron Park, speaking.
Come this way.
[zombies growling]
And enjoy your stay.
[zombies snarling]
[pleasant music playing]
[whimpering]
[shuddering]
[Young-joo panting]
[gasps]
[whirring]
- [whirring stops]
- [gasps]
[exhales] Jae-yoon, hey!
Hey!
[sobbing]
[wailing]
I was so scared without you.
I was alone with those zombies.
How are you? Are you okay?
Have you been hurt?
Hey, you're acting weird. What's going on?
[tense music playing]
Young-joo.
- [bones cracking]
- [grunts]
- [gasps, cries]
- [Jae-yoon] Listen to me.
before it's too late, kill me.
[raspy breathing]
I can't. I can't hurt you. I just can't.
[growling]
[gasps]
- [crying]
- [chainsaw whirring]
Please, set me free. [screams]
[Jae-yoon] Young-joo.
[growling]
[Young-joo screaming]
[gasps]
Ahh!
[panting]
[door opens, closes]
We're over here.
[all panting]
[Gye-young sighs]
Good, you're all here.
Hold on. Where'd Paolo go?
[exclaims]
[Arron Park] There're zombies there.
We can't go there!
- We can get down through here.
- [Jae-yoon] Okay, okay.
[Young-man] Watch your step.
[Jae-yoon] Arron Park, take my hand.
- [whimpers]
- [In-ho] Please go faster.
- [Arron Park] We'll turn and go through.
- [Jae-yoon] Okay.
[rattles]
[panting]
We're clear. Come on.
[thudding]
[grunting]
[exhales]
[continues panting]
[In-ho] Thank you.
[grunting]
[Arron Park] Okay. [exhales]
- Soo-jeong. It's okay. Come on.
- [Soo-jeong] Hmm? [grunts]
[Jae-yoon exclaims]
- [both] It's okay.
- [Jae-yoon] I caught your helmet.
I'm coming down.
[Arron Park] That's it.
[Gye-young] Shit.
- Hey, hold on. What happened to your arm?
- Wha-- Oh.
It's nothing.
I must've scratched it crawling around.
That's a bullet wound. Did you get hit?
Well, yeah, but I'm okay, honestly.
- Hey, come here.
- Oh, okay.
[Gye-young] Son of a bitch.
[helmet thuds on floor]
Hey.
Are you insane? Huh?
You didn't think it could ricochet?
Hey, Kwak Gye-young, just relax.
If it weren't for him, we would've died.
Yeah, I get it.
He still shouldn't have done that.
Thank God that Soo-jeong
only has a little mark.
If your aim was any worse,
she would be dead.
Fucking asshole!
Just shut up already!
Hey!
What did you say?
[scoffs]
You turn off your hearing aid?
Shut the fuck up, you stupid motherfucker!
You son of a bitch! You wanna die?
What the fuck? What are you gonna do?
- [Gye-young] Take that back.
- Huh?
- What's wrong with you, son?
- I'm not your son. Jesus Christ.
Why the hell are you calling me son,
when we're not even friends?
Hey.
What's going on, dude?
[scoffs] Son of a bitch.
Oh, fucking hell.
[exhales]
You're still pretending? Huh?
How long are we gonna play training camp
while the world is ending?
- [In-ho exclaims]
- [Kyung-sik] Huh?
Literally Nothing.
We're doing matters now.
The world is fucked.
I don't give a fuck what you think.
[groans]
What the fuck is this guy's issue?
[gun cocks]
Kwak Gye-young...
Do you want to die?
Wanna test my aim and see this bullet
- fly out the back of your head.
- Drop the gun!
Shut your mouth, asshole!
Stay there if you don't want me
to shoot you.
Drop the gun
if you don't want me to shoot.
Drop the gun or I'll paint
this entire tower with your head!
I will. All right.
I'm just kidding. I'm kidding.
- [Gye-young] Holy fuck.
- Seriously. It's a joke.
[exhales]
I was just kidding.
Why was everybody so scared?
- Fuck you fucking lunatic!
- Hey.
Gye-young. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Hey.
Look.
If you don't wanna show us
any respect... don't.
We won't show you any either.
[chuckles]
Do whatever you want.
[both chuckling]
All right, listen up.
[tense music playing]
Whatever's going on,
we don't have time for it.
We need to get out of here
right now, don't we?
So, first of all,
this is a construction site,
so there's a freight elevator in here.
In theory, it would be connected
to the underground lot,
so if we find it,
we can all get out of here.
Now let's all fan out and look for it.
[exhales] Yeah, fan out and start looking.
- Understood, sir.
[Young-joo panting]
[zombies snarling]
[continues panting]
[music playing]
[man] ♪ It feels like I'm born again ♪
♪ Everything about me has changed ♪
♪ After I met you, I became a new person ♪
♪ My mom is surprised the most ♪
♪ First, I wake up early in the morning ♪
♪ And play the music that you suggested ♪
♪ I don't know it is but I like it... ♪
- [woman 1 gasps]
- [man 1] Huh?
- Who's she?
- [man 2] I thought it was locked.
[man 3] Well, I guess not.
- Did anyone open the door?
- [man 2] No.
- [woman 2] Who are you?
- [man 3] What if she's bit?
- [woman 3] Should we run?
- [gasps] Yoon Jong-shin?
- [woman 4] She knows him?
- Are you safe?
[man 4] He knows her.
[flashlight clicks]
[Young-man] All right.
So what do we do next? Huh?
[Soo-jeong] Is there another way out?
- [Gye-young] Haven't seen any.
- [Young-man sighs]
[gasping]
Dude, I found something.
I found a...
[Jae-yoon] What is it this time?
What?
[In-ho] It's a gondola!
Wha-- The box is still on.
- This thing still works, I bet.
- Looks like it.
It goes to the ground level.
Can take it there?
Yeah, I think it'll make it.
[sighs] If one of us finds
a way to get there
and press that button,
we could load our gear up,
hop in and ride it down home free!
And who's that?
Who's gonna do it?
[comical music playing]
Ra In-ho, who?
Well?
Anyone?
- Are you up for it?
- No.
- [Jae-yoon] Huh? You?
- Nope.
[Soo-jeong clears throat]
[Jae-yoon] I knew it would be you.
[heroic music playing]
[Arron Park inhales, exhales]
Thank you so much.
I think I had a few too many drinks.
[heroic music concludes]
Shit.
Huh? Uh... I don't...
That's how we say hello.
Are you staying safe out there?
Oh, uh, yeah, for sure.
Mr. Yoon. How in the world
did you get here?
If you wanna die, go somewhere else.
- Uh... I'm sorry.
- We keep the door locked here.
Ah!
I was heading to an awards
show down the street...
- with some goofy clothes on.
- Oh, no, you look great.
- [chuckles]
- [Jong-shin] Welcome.
[Young-joo grunts]
How 'bout another round? Oh, my...
You don't need to worry about anything.
Just stay here. It's the only way to live.
[Young-joo exhales]
[Jong-shin] So what should
I sing for you next?
[breathes deeply]
[wind whooshing]
[breathing heavily]
[yelps]
[whimpers]
Oh, shit. Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait.
Wait. [yelps]
[grunts]
[yelps]
Shit. [breathing shakily]
[Arron Park sighs]
[In-ho whimpering]
[yelps]
[all exclaiming]
[In-ho] Shit!
- [thuds]
- [all shouting]
Oh, my God. Holy shit.
[Young-man on radio]
Jae-yoon, are you okay?
- [Soo-jeong] Are you okay?
- [Gye-young] He's standing.
[Arron Park] Are you okay?
[Soo-jeong] Say something, please.
[Young-man] Answer me, Private.
Answer, come on.
This is Private Lee. The gondola is on.
- [all exclaiming]
- [Arron Park] Oh, my God. He made it.
- [somber music playing]
- [radio static buzzing]
[somber music continues]
[sobbing]
♪ Annie, will you hear me on the radio ♪
♪ The Annie I'm singing of is you... ♪
[man 1] We're gonna get out.
It'll be okay.
♪ I'll confess ♪
[woman sobbing]
♪ The feelings in my heart ♪
♪ Forever on my mind ♪
♪ You are ♪
- ♪ Annie ♪
- [chuckles]
♪ Will you hear me on the radio ♪
♪ The Annie I'm singing of is you... ♪
[Young-joo] Huh?
[gasps]
♪ The feelings in my heart ♪
[Young-joo] When did he take this?
♪ Forever on my mind ♪
♪ You are ♪
♪ Hey ♪
♪ You charming clown... ♪
[Jae-yoon speaking indistinctly on video]
[Jae-yoon] Young-joo...
["Annie" by Yoon Jong-shin
playing on speakers]
[sniffles] Young-joo, I, uh...
I wanna ask you to wait
until I'm out of the military.
♪ You cured my lifelong pain ♪
But I know that's unfair.
♪ Yes, you're the one
who made me smile again ♪
If we end up having to...
go our separate ways...
♪ I love you more than you could... ♪
...there'll be no hard feelings, okay?
Your happiness is
all that matters. I'll be okay.
♪ You cured my lifelong pain... ♪
Whether we're in a relationship or not...
♪ Who made me smile again... ♪
You are the entire world to me.
[Jae-yoon on video]
That's never gonna change.
- Thank you, Young-joo.
- [sobbing]
♪ The Annie I'm singing of is you ♪
[cell phone screen locks]
♪ I'll confess ♪
♪ The feelings in my heart ♪
- [sobbing]
- ♪ Forever on my mind... ♪
[Arron Park] Private Lee Jae-yoon.
Button. Button. Push the button.
- [Gye-young] You got this.
- Yes, press the button.
Please.
Oh, God. Please work.
- [gondola thudding, whirring]
- [exclaims]
It's working. [cheers]
[all cheering]
[Soo-jeong] He really did it!
[all shouting in excitement]
Oh, thank you. [sighs] Oh, my God.
- [Soo-jeong cheering]
- [Gye-young laughs] He did it.
You did it.
[grunts]
Nice, a chainsaw strap.
Oh!
[gasps]
A scooter, too? There we go.
[grunts]
[Young-joo] All set here.
[Jong-shin] Hey, there.
Wherever you're going, I believe in you.
Take care now, okay?
Will do, and you guys, too.
[woman] Take care of yourself, okay?
Be safe out there.
[scooter whirring]
[Jae-yoon] Young-joo.
- Young-joo.
- Jae-yoon.
[gondola squeaking]
[Gye-young yelps]
[Soo-jeong breathes deeply]
[In-ho whimpering]
[Arron Park] It's okay. It's okay.
All right, we're almost there.
Almost there.
[In-ho whimpers, cries]
Yes.
[Jae-yoon] In-ho.
We're close to the bottom.
- You okay?
- We can see the ground.
- We're almost there.
- [Gye-young] Yeah.
[Arron Park] We're almost there.
- [Young-man] Almost there.
- [Arron Park] Any second.
- [Gye-young] Wait.
- [gondola thuds]
[all exclaiming in fear]
- What's happening?
- [Young-man] What's wrong?
We're still safe on this thing, right?
This was supposed to be fixed.
- Huh? When?
- Holy shit.
Today.
- Huh? What?
- [Jae-yoon] For Christ's sake.
We're gonna die.
- [Jae-yoon] Hold on.
- [Young-man] Hold on, tight.
- [Gye-young crying]
- We're not far away.
Hey, look down! Look. We're so close.
- [Jae-yoon] Almost there.
- [Soo-jeong] We're okay.
- Please, please.
[all screaming]
[gasps] Hey! What?
- Why'd it stop?
- [Gye-young] Why isn't the moving?
[Young-man] What's wrong with this thing?
[In-ho] It won't fall if we stay still!
[overlapping conversations]
Guys!
- [Soo-jeong gasps]
- I went to school for this.
- [Gye-young] Mechanical engineering
- [Young-man] That's right.
[Arron Park] Is it busted?
[In-ho] Jae-yoon's got something!
Wha-- What?
- I have no idea what's wrong.
- [all exclaiming in fear]
- [overlapping shouting]
- [In-ho screaming]
[Young-man] Calm down.
We're gonna be fine.
We'll find another way.
[Arron Park] I can't believe this.
We almost made it.
- [Soo-jeong] You have to fix it.
- [Young-man] Just relax, man.
[zombies snarling]
- [Young-man] Whoa!
- [Gye-young whimpers] Whoa!
- [grunts]
- Hey! Get away.
- Get!
- [snarls]
- Oh, my God!
[Soo-jeong] No, just go back over there.
[Young-man] Oh, God.
Hurry away from the window.
[Soo-jeong] If he breaks the window...
[Young-man] Hey! Move!
[control box beeping]
[Gye-young yelps] What do we do?
[In-ho whimpers]
[Gye-young yelps] Oh, God. There's more.
[all shouting in panic]
[Young-man] Jae-yoon, do something.
[Soo-jeong] We gotta get out.
[Arron Park] Fix the fucking control box.
[control box beeps, and clicks]
- [whirring]
- Oh shit, it worked!
- It worked!
- [all cheering]
[overlapping cheering]
[Arron Park shouting indistinctly]
Hey, we're almost there!
Just a little bit more.
I thought I was dead. [cries]
- [Arron Park laughing]
- [Young-man] Wait, hold on.
- [Gye-young] Just stay still.
- [Young man] Can it go faster?
[Arron Park] What's that?
Hey, look up there!
[zombies growling]
[cracking]
[Gye-young] Wait a minute.
[snarling]
[all screaming]
[yell echoing]
[scooter whirring]
[zombies snarling]
[Young-joo yelps]
[screaming]
Jesus Christ!
[zombies continue snarling]
[Young-joo screaming]
[whimpers]
[gasps]
[zombies hissing]
Jesus.
[Jae-yoon] Young-joo.
There's only one way out.
Through.
[saw whirring]
- [crackling]
- [gondola creaking]
[thudding]
[all yelping]
[Soo-jeong screaming]
[all grunting]
[zombies snarling]
[Kyung-sik grunting]
[Gye-young yelps]
[Young-man grunting]
- [Soo-jeong shouts]
- Incoming.
[Soo-jeong grunts]
[Jae-yoon yelps]
[zombie snarling]
[In-ho] Please, somebody. Jesus Christ.
- [screaming]
- Ra In-ho!
[zombie snarling]
[Arron Park grunts]
[zombies snarls]
- [In-ho whimpers]
- [Arron Park] Private In-ho!
[In-ho screaming]
[Arron Park and Jae-yoon grunting]
[Jae-yoon yells]
[continues yelling]
- [zombie snarling]
- [Soo-jeong grunting]
- [zombie growls]
- [gunshot fires]
[Soo-jeong gasps]
Wait, wait, it's getting up again!
[Kyung-sik and Young-man grunting]
- Die, bitch!
- [GYe-young] Young-man!
- [pulley clanks]
- [all shouting]
[yelping, screaming]
[thudding]
[Young-man] Oh, my God.
[all panting]
[gondola creaking]
Oh, my God.
Get out of here! Come on!
Everybody hurry!
- Come on, come on.
- [Jae-yoon] Go, go.
Hurry!
- [In-ho] It's finally over.
- [Arron Park] Go.
- Let's go. Come on.
- Everyone out.
- Hurry, come on. Be careful.
- [Soo-jeong] Come on.
- You're okay.
- There you go.
- [gondola rumbling]
- [yelps]
[screaming]
Shit! Hold on.
[all shouting]
[Soo-jeong] No! Jae-yoon!
[Jae-yoon yelping]
Jae-yoon. Come back up!
- [Soo-jeong] Oh, God.
- [Jae-yoon screaming]
- [whimpering]
- [gondola creaking]
[yelping]
[screaming]
[thudding]
[gondola crashing]
[zombies growling]
[gondola rumbling]
[cables whipping]
[zombies growling]
[Kyung-sik panting]
Huh.
God!
[Soo-jeong sobbing]
Okay,
- Shit, man.
- [In-ho] Hey.
Jae--
- Lee Jae-yoon, are you alive?
- [yells]
Jae-yoon, Jae-yoon.
Jae-yoon.
Jae-yoon has to come back up.
[Soo-jeong crying]
[whirring]
[Young-joo panting] Oh, shit.
[continues panting]
[Jae-yoon] Young-joo.
EXIT
Oh, shit.
[Jae-yoon] Young-joo.
If you follow the tracks
you'll find Suseo Station.
Oh! [chuckles]
Good idea.
[zombies growling]
[Young-joo gasps]
Oh, fuck me.
[tense music playing]
[chainsaw whirring]
[zombies snarling]
[shouts, screams]
[grunting]
[panting]
[grunts]
[sniffles]
[Jae-yoon] Young-joo. [echoing]
[Young-joo gasps]
[exhales, exclaims in disgust]
- [thudding on door]
- [zombies growling]
[tense music playing]
Private Lee Jae-yoon...
could still be alive on the third floor.
There's no way he didn't make it.
Corporal, I'm gonna need
your reserve bullets.
Hey, hey.
Lee Jae-yoon's a dead man.
He fell from here.
No one would survive that fall.
So shut the fuck up, Ra In-ho.
You're a fucking dick.
'Cause nothing affects you, right?
Of course not.
Jae-yoon died trying to save us.
- Do you realize that?
- Get off me.
A lot of people die that way.
Why didn't you do something
instead of losing your shit?
Stand back now, Hwang Kyung-sik.
[Gye-young sobbing]
[sniffles]
[exhales]
Lee Jae-yoon...
he's finished.
[all gasp]
- He's fucking gone.
- Hey!
[breathing shakily]
[sobbing]
[Soo-jeong grunts]
[Kyung-sik] Don't be so upset.
Stop whining and help figure out
how the hell we're gonna get out of here!
Don't give me this crap right now.
Crying about it is gonna change.
What happened?
[In-ho crying]
[Arron Park softly] Hey.
You're a fucking sociopath, Kyung-sik.
Come on, come on, come on.
- Shit!
- [Young-man] Stop it!
[zombies snarling]
[tense music playing]
[zombies growling]
[thudding]
[grunts]
Ah, shit! [grunting]
What? Who are you?
What the fuck are you doing?
Hey! Get off of me!
What are you-- [grunting]
Who the fuck are you? Hey!
All right. You know what? Little shit.
What the hell is going on? Fuck!
What are you, nuts?
Come here. Come here.
Fucking thing.
- [growling]
- That was a mistake.
[yelps]
[breathing shakily]
[zombie continues growling]
[sighs]
What?
[exhales]
Huh?
MONDAY, MAY 5TH
3:08
Young-joo.
[breathing shakily]
[breathing heavily]
[zombies growling]
[banging on window]
[growling continues]
- [subway door opens]
- [footsteps approaching]
- [chainsaw whirring]
- Hey, hold on.
Listen, wait a second.
Don't worry. I'm not a monster.
Come on. I'm a human.
[whirring stops]
[Young-joo breathing shakily]
I'm sorry, miss.
I didn't mean to scare you.
Uh, it's okay.
Sir, what are you doing down here alone?
Oh, right.
Uh, well, I'm looking for my daughter.
Huh?
- [Jae-yoon] Young-joo.
- [Young-joo gasps]
- Run!
[man 1] We're done with this side.
[man 2] We've cut off the heads.
It's a lot harder than you think.
- [man 3] Look there.
- [man 4] What the hell?
- [man 3] What's going on?
- [man 1] Sir, you okay?
- [man 5] Ooh. [laughs]
- [man 3] Shit.
[man 1] You're alone. Oh, no!
[man 5] What the fuck is that?
Is that a zombie?
- [man 3] Where you going?
- [man 5 grunts]
- [clanks]
- [Young-joo shouts]
[all laughing]
[man 4] Man, she just doesn't
wanna go down.
[man 3] So brave.
- [sighs] We here we go.
- [Young-joo whimpers]
[men exclaiming]
- [man 3] Score.
- What's wrong with you?
- What are you doing?
- Uh, there's a lot of blood,
but no wounds,
at least from what I can see.
Sir, how do you want us
to take care of this?
The wounds aside, there's no way
she's okay with all that blood.
She's human now,
but she'll turn eventually.
Just do what we usually do.
[man 2] Yes, sir.
You heard him.
Cut her head off.
Yes, sir!
Oh, shit. Fuck, yeah!
This is just like that one Texas movie.
God, I've always wanted to try this.
- Fuck, yeah! [chuckles]
- This is gonna be sick.
- [chainsaw whirring]
- Ready to die?
- [screams]
- [all exclaim]
- [man 1] What was that?
- [man 2] Did you throw this crowbar?
Yeah? You got ten seconds to run. Got it?
- Ten, nine...
- [man 3] Fuck she's fast.
[man 2] Let's go. Fuck!
[gasps, pants]
Ra In-ho!
Are you there Sergeant Kim?
If you can hear me, I'm alive!
Oh, fuck.
[thudding]
[snarling]
[sighs]
Wait...
[snarling]
There we go.
[snarls]
[thuds]
[snarling]
[thudding and snarling]
[exhales]
[Jae-yoon] This is it.
All set.
This is it. This is it.
[screaming]
Young-joo!
[music playing]